Ms. Zoe is here to thank you
Your secret feed formula
Is truly excellent
Five tons a day
Demand exceeds supply
You must be mistaken
I never sold
The formula to Ms. Zoe
I told you
Whatever I want
I always get
If you won't sell
I'll still find a way
Brother-in-law
Did you think you were safe by being careful
I had my parents
Play the victim at your place
While your guard was down
We put cameras
In your mixing room
Every ingredient you mixed
Was caught on tape
You're so ungrateful
Ms. Zoe offered you
200,000 back then but you refused
Now you won't get a cent
Ms. Zoe has already patented it
Selling it now is infringement
Daniel
Are you even human
Helping an outsider plot against family
Don't mention family to me
When I was struggling
Did any of you help me
You're no relatives of mine
However
Since this formula
Got me in Ms. Zoe's good graces
When you buy our feed
I'll give you 20 percent off
You
He's not worth getting angry at
Besides
He's not the mastermind
To get what she wants
Ms. Zoe stops at nothing
But
Do you really think you've won